(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Space Rice Cake)
(They excitedly opened up for their 2nd day of business.)
(Space Rice Cake launched a new menu.)
(Broccolino Basiliano)
(The vibrant light green color is an eye-catcher.)
(It's called basil tteokbokki.)
(As soon as it launched, the praises poured in.)
(They opened with full confidence and high spirits, but...)
(Flustered)
(They hit an unexpected snag with the hard rice cakes.)
(And the customers kept on flooding in.)
(Customers keep coming in slowly, just like Grand Prince Suyang.)
(The crowd with the fierce vibe of Grand Prince Suyang want to order.)
(Yu Jin comes right away.)
Take your time with the menu and feel free to ask me...
- Jade Emperor Tteokbokki...
- Yes.
Please feel free to ask me anything.
Two of that and one pomegranate slushy, please.
- Would you like any soda with that?
- No.
Okay. Got it.
One pomegranate slushy...
- and one tteokramisu chestnut, yes?
- Yes.
- Coming right up.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- If you like mala tteokbokki, - Yes.
- I totally recommend it. Yes.
- Really?
- We got orders.
- Okay.
All right. Hit us with the orders.
(Tteokbokki Order Status: two small original tteokbokki, )
(one small basil tteokbokki, one small mala tteokbokki)
One small basil tteokbokki.
(It's a bolt out of the blue.)
- Coming right up.
- Okay.
Look at this green onion that Yu Jin chopped.
It's okay.
I didn't know Yu Jin was still here.
- I didn't give you something?
- No.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
- Whatever it is, I'm sorry.
- I love you, Yu Jin.
- That's okay.
- I just wanted to say I love you.
I really love you.
(She starts making tteokbokki before getting caught.)
This is a bit too much of the sauce, but...
Good. The rice cakes are in.
Is today a special day or something?
(Basil tteokbokki on the other side)
- We'll be off.
- Yes. Thank you.
(Every single burner is fully ignited.)
The rice cakes went in.
(Tteokbokki Progress: Original and basil, in progress)
(Mala, pending)
- This cuts through the greasiness.
- It's good.
(The customers outside are ready for dessert now.)
- It'll be ready shortly.
- Hold on.
(But there's still no sign of the desserts coming out.)
Fishcakes.
They didn't forget about our tteokramisu, right?
Good. Thank you.
I'm practicing.
(She's a bit slow since it's her first time, but she's thorough.)
(She looks more serious than ever since the grand opening.)
(The next step is...)
(to add a generous layer of chestnut powder.)
(Eun Ji's first tteokramisu chestnut)
(Like a squirrel storing acorns, she gathers the desserts.)
(She keeps the spare desserts nice and cool in the fridge.)
(Right after that, she serves the rest.)
It's topped with a whole chestnut.
That's right. Yes.
(They take a big bite after waiting eagerly.)
This is the perfect dessert after the spicy dish.
Yes.
It's good.
The ocean breeze feels so great.
(The ocean breeze blows by...)
(to dry Young Ji's sweat...)
(and cool down the heat.)
I'm turning the heat up a little.
This burner won't light.
(The sky looks absolutely clear, )
(but the weather in this area is...)
(It's expected to stay sunny...)
(from morning to afternoon, )
(sitting right at 22°C...)
(with a wind at the speed of 2.7m per second.)
(It's a gentle breeze.)
(But since we're near the ocean, the wind can be a lot stronger.)
(That's it for today's weather forecast...)
(Help me.)
(Thanks to that wind, she's fighting a battle against nature.)
Everytime I put it on low heat, the fire just blows out.
Right.
- That's what's happening right now.
- But I need to cook it on low heat.
(The wind keeps blowing, leaving Young Ji flustered.)
(The flame is flickering again.)
(The fire blows out.)
It went out again. This is annoying.
- I've got this.
- You've got this.
That happens.
(She's not angry.)
(Tteokbokki Progress: Original, in progress, basil, fire out, )
(mala, not even on the stove yet)
(Thinking about the customers who are waiting for their food...)
I've changed my strategy.
(You must stay calm at times like this!)
Please give me a moment.
Trust me.
I trust you.
(She adjusts the heat with Chef Mimi's help.)
The rice cakes look bouncy.
(When the tteokbokki is simmered down to perfection...)
- Thank you.
- They're hot. Be careful.
- Got it.
- Be careful.
- Small original tteokbokki is up.
- Okay.
- Original tteokbokki is coming out.
Another small original tteokbokki is ready.
Basil tteokbokki is ready.
(Tteokbokki Progress: Mala, cooking starts now)
It's my first time getting an order for a small portion of this.
(She puts rice cakes in the pot skillfully.)
(Then, she simmers it down.)
- It's already too late.
- Why so busy today?
(There's something missing here.)
(She forgot beef loin again.)
Oh, right. Okay.
(But it's not okay without beef loin.)
The mala tteokbokki will be ready in one minute.
Young Ji, isn't mala tteokbokki supposed to...
have beef loin?
(She's done for.)
(It's already simmered down. It's too late to cook beef loin.)
(What do I do?)
- Can you grill beef loin for me?
- Okay.
(She boldly changes the recipe.)
Thank you.
(They get right into the plan.)
(Sous Chef Duties: Pollack roe and clam pasta, fried sides, )
(cheering up the head chef, grilling beef loin)
(She puts beef loin in the frying pan.)
A fistful of beef loin? It's okay.
(While Mimi is stir-frying the meat quickly...)
(Meanwhile, Young Ji...)
(adds the rest of the toppings.)
(Grand Prince Suyang solo table: Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki)
(Lonely)
- The tteokbokki will be ready soon.
- It's okay. Take your time.
- She's waiting for mala tteokbokki.
- It's ready.
- Oh, okay.
Just give me 20 seconds.
(Finally, the beef loin is ready.)
Stack it up nicely. Thank you.
(Adding the toppings...)
- Let's use this only for the meat.
- Mala tteokbokki is ready.
Thank you for waiting.
(Tteokbokki Progress: Original and basil, ready and served, )
(mala, ready)
Hello. I can take your payment here.
- Thank you. Go home safely.
- Thank you. Bye.
(The first customers from the opening time head out.)
(The next wave of customers enters, leaving no tables empty.)
- Hello. I'm sorry for the wait.
- Hello.
Oh, my. Yu Jin, the owner of the general store is here.
- My goodness. Welcome.
- Ma'am, you weren't there earlier.
- You weren't there earlier.
- Will you give us more free food?
The owner of the general store is here...
This is amazing. Please give me a second.
(She quickly leaves to avoid an awkward situation.)
- How many in your party?
- Four.
Please give me a moment.
Your table is ready inside.
(Large parties are rolling in one after another.)
We've got 2 new parties of 4 and 5.
- Let's see how it goes for now.
- Okay.
- Are you ready to order?
- Yes.
- Hello.
- All right.
Can we have one of everything?
Please give me a second.
(She's taken aback by these big eaters.)
(Sensing the looming disaster, she gets her gear ready.)
- Will you try the "Don't Eat" one?
- Yes.
Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.
- Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.
- Yes.
Has anyone taken your order yet?
- May I take your order?
- Okay.
Yes, please. We'd like to try something you recommend.
- Then...
- If it's not good, we'll return it.
- That won't happen. I'm confident.
- She sounds confident.
I recommend one medium original tteokbokki...
- We serve basil tteokbokki now.
- I see.
Focus, everyone. We got another order.
One small original tteokbokki,
one medium Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki,
one medium pollack roe and clam pasta,
one tteokramisu chestnut, one of each slushy,
and one small Broccolino Basiliano.
Wait. Can you repeat it just once?
(Order Status: 2 original, 1 mala, 2 basil tteokbokki, )
(1 pasta, 1 tteokramisu chestnut, 2 slushies)
(It's a lot.)
(However...)
Hello.
Hello. Are there two in your party?
Broccolino Basiliano...
- One small portion.
- Yes.
- We got an order. A new order.
- Thank you.
A new order? No way.
One medium original tteokbokki,
one medium Broccolino Basiliano,
- and three pomegranate slushies.
- No way. You're lying.
- Okay. Got it.
- Okay.
(Tteokbokki Order Status: 2 original, 2 mala, 3 basil)
(She hasn't even started cooking a single one.)
I'll change my cooking gloves.
- Good attitude toward hygiene.
- Right.
I keep getting the sauce on my hands.
(Mimi scans the kitchen with the eye of a hawk.)
I want to check if people like my tteokbokki.
They're all cold now.
One, two, three. One, two, three, four, five.
(After lining up the fried food, )
(she starts cooking pollack roe and clam pasta.)
I guess we're dealing with two large parties right now.
(The special sauce for original tteokbokki)
(Chili bean sauce and Sichuan pepper oil for mala tteokbokki)
(Making the base for basil tteokbokki)
(The three-pot system is on.)
(But...)
The burner with the mala tteokbokki went out.
Okay.
(The burner is acting up again.)
It's doing this to me on purpose.
It wants me to go through ordeals.
(Young Ji's Ordeal 1: The delayed wait time)
I'm way too experienced for this.
Oh, we're out of sausages.
Gosh, my back hurts.
(Young Ji's Ordeal 2: Running out of ingredients)
What's going on? What's the matter?
(Young Ji's Ordeal 3: Hard rice cakes)
Calm down.
- Calm down. It's okay.
- Calm down.
(And here's our dear sous chef.)
Where is my thermometer?
(Believe it or not, Mimi mixes English with Korean when flustered.)
(While the kitchen is in chaos...)
(The table is empty.)
(She drinks dongchimi while waiting for the food.)
Are they making rice cakes to make the dishes?
(We do make our own rice cakes, but we're not doing it right now.)
(The kitchen still needs more time.)
(What they need right now is...)
I'm sorry for the delay.
- It'll take just a bit longer, - That's okay.
So we prepared these for you. They're on the house.
- They're coffee slushies. Try them.
- Thanks.
- Hello?
- Please wait just a bit longer.
The owner of the general store is here, but I've been way too busy...
with customers to properly take care of you. I'm sorry.
- Come on. Don't be like this.
- I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
- That's okay.
- I'm a fan of yours.
- That's me.
- That's her.
(Eun Ji buys time for the kitchen by chatting with her fans.)
- That's me.
- I told you so.
- Please wait just a bit longer.
- Sure.
(She's so pretty.)
Just looking at her makes you feel full, right?
(Yu Jin appeases the customers' hunger with her cuteness.)
We don't have enough pots for small portions.
(While the chefs are flustered...)
(Yu Jin runs to the kitchen with her apron fluttering.)
You have two pots here.
Thank you, Yu Jin.
Please call me the fairy of pots.
(While the service team runs around busily...)
(to buy time for the chefs...)
- Small original tteokbokki is up.
- Okay.
- I'll cook beef loin.
- Here's small original tteokbokki.
Medium ghost pepper tteokbokki is ready.
Pollack roe and clam pasta is ready.
Here's the small original tteokbokki.
- Your tteokbokki is here.
- It finally came out.
I know. You waited so long, right? I'm very sorry.
It came out fast.
(It's time to taste it quickly.)
(Impressed)
- Is it good?
- Yes, it's good.
(Fortunately, they don't look like they'll send it back.)
This could be a brilliant business item.
It's good.
(The big eaters are tasting the food as well.)
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's good. It tastes like my mom's food.
- Hang on a second.
- I'm serious.
- Great.
- Nice.
- I just...
- We're doing great.
I just heard a really touching review...
from the table that ordered everything. Can I tell you guys now?
- Sure. Go ahead.
- Yes.
It was so touching.
(She's choked with emotion even before sharing the review.)
A customer said the food tasted like his mother's food.
(It's hard to say if that's good or bad.)
- Really?
- He also said he'd think of you...
- as his mother just for today.
- Really?
Oh, my. Really? It's a compliment, right?
Young Ji, who is only 25,
captured the true essence of a mother's cooking.
Oh, my. That's hard to believe.
- I applaud her achievement.
- Exactly. It's incredible.
He said it tasted like his mother's food.
Basil tteokbokki is remaining.
Can you serve the basil tteokbokki as well, Yu Jin?
- It'll be perfect timing.
- It's almost ready.
First ready, first served.
- Pepper.
- Cha, cha, La cucaracha
- La cucaracha, la cucaracha - Pepper.
(Never look up the word.)
You're doing great.
Can I take it now?
- You can take it. Let's go.
- Okay.
Store owner, here I come.
- Order complete for their table.
- That's a wrap on their table.
(Tteokbokki Order Status: Ready and served)
(Remaining)
What is this again?
- Basil.
- It's basil tteokbokki.
(They try their first basil tteokbokki.)
- The color is just like Shrek's.
- Right.
It's not every day you get to taste a famous chef's cooking.
- It's tasty.
- It's good.
(The customers enjoy the food even though it's new to them.)
(They already finished their food.)
We'd like to settle up.
Yes, sir. I'll be right with you.
- Please come again.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you. Have a happy day.
Hello. Welcome. How many in your party?
- Three.
- Three? Just a moment. I'm sorry.
- This way, please.
- Thank you.
(Teenage customers are here.)
We make our own rice cakes every morning.
We do that because our head chef said,
"We'll just make rice cakes." That was a mistake.
- May I sit here for a moment?
- Sure.
(After breaking the ice, she sneaks into a seat.)
And one medium pollack roe and clam pasta, please.
(She comes out after taking the teens' order.)
Table Five...
- Has your food not come out yet?
- No.
I see. Please give me a moment.
I'll run to the kitchen and rush the head chef.
If we get tteokbokki too, is that going to be too much?
- Would you like a small portion?
- Yes, please.
- Sure. I will...
- Thank you.
No problem. I'll add that to your order.
Chef Lee, we got an additional order.
- Okay.
- For Table Five,
one small original tteokbokki.
- Got it.
- The remaining ones are...
- one small basil tteokbokki, - A small portion.
- one small mala tteokbokki, - One small mala tteokbokki.
- And one small original tteokbokki.
- It'd be better...
It'd be better if we could serve the ghost pepper tteokbokki first.
The ghost pepper tteokbokki will be ready in one minute.
- I mean, two minutes.
- Okay.
(Mala tteokbokki was ordered by two tables.)
(Eun Ji referred to the medium portion for the teens' table.)
(And Young Ji is talking about the small one for the couple.)
(One of those tables might not get their food at this rate.)
Can I take this now? Should I clean up the table?
- It'll be ready when you're back.
- Okay.
- Medium ghost pepper tteokbokki.
- Thank you.
Medium ghost pepper tteokbokki?
- I was talking to myself.
- Oh, okay.
We haven't made any mistakes so far.
(Hello. I am that mistake.)
What's wrong with you?
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(Medium mala tteokbokki is omitted.)
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
Can I get a straw, please?
Of course. I'll give you 2, not just 1.
(A customer asks for help with a tiny voice.)
- Here's a straw for you.
- Thank you.
No problem.
- Put it in this cup.
- It's over there.
(The medium mala tteokbokki table is filling up on slushy.)
Is the medium ghost pepper tteokbokki coming out?
It's a small portion, Eun Ji.
They ordered one more tiramisu.
- Table Two.
- And so...
Wait, why is the ghost pepper tteokbokki small?
Isn't the ghost pepper tteokbokki small?
No, Table One ordered a medium.
- Why is it a small?
- Is this ready?
Which table ordered a small?
- Mala tteokbokki.
- I'll erase it for you.
- Thank you.
- It's mala tteokbokki.
It's because I wrote "mala tteokbokki."
- I see.
- It's correct.
- Isn't it a small size?
- Is it a small?
- Yes, it is.
(Eun Ji thought that it was only medium mala tteokbokki.)
- Is it correct?
- The name is difficult.
- We'll change the name tonight.
- Let's change it.
Table One ordered medium ghost pepper tteokbokki.
Can we say that there's one more medium ghost pepper tteokbokki?
- Yes.
- That's right.
(Thankfully, they sorted everything out without missing any orders.)
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(Omitted medium mala tteokbokki returns.)
(Meanwhile, another customer walks in.)
I'm so sorry. I'll clean it up right away.
I'm sorry.
It's only our second day, so we're a little overwhelmed.
It will be one small ghost pepper tteokbokki.
(1 small ghost pepper tteokbokki, 1 small original tteokbokki...)
Thank you.
(Exclaiming)
All this trash came out of my pocket.
Small ghost pepper tteokbokki is ready.
I'll take that.
Wait. My goodness.
- I'll leave it here.
- Hold on a second.
(Eun Ji's to-do list)
Where is it?
(Concentrating hard while furrowing her brow)
Table Five.
(Looking quite intimidating)
Here's your Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.
Could you move the burner toward the center?
- The burner...
- I see.
I wouldn't ask for your number, would I?
Be careful. It's hot.
- It looks good.
- I'll bring you small plates.
Enjoy your food.
(Current Time: 2:55pm)
(5 minutes before the last order)
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(Remaining: 2 small original, 1 medium mala, 1 small mala)
Wait a minute. A medium mala...
We also have one small original tteokbokki.
Is there small original tteokbokki too?
Yes, we got it as another order.
We're out of pots for original tteokbokki.
We're out of pots.
(Everything is starting to run out.)
The original...
(Yu Jin is serving dongchimi.)
Gosh, I'm out of bowls for dongchimi.
(Hunting for hidden bowls for dongchimi)
Look how fast the fried food is going out.
Oh, no. We're out of fried toppings.
(The prepared fried food starts running out.)
(She burns what's left.)
I thought I had already taken it out.
(Crying her eyes out)
This is...
(As the ingredients...)
It's insane.
(And everyone's mental energy is running out.)
We can do it.
(Everyone is finally making a run for the finish line.)
Oh, no. This is so unfortunate.
Didn't you hear the news?
(A customer already walked in.)
Oh, my gosh.
We are two minutes away from last order.
Two minutes away? Please come on in.
(They give a warm welcome, but their bodies say otherwise.)
- How many are you?
- I'm alone.
Welcome. Come this way.
(You're always welcome at Space Rice Cake.)
One small original tteokbokki.
One coffee slushy.
I'm about to cry.
Mimi, is this it?
- Wait.
- Right now...
I just have to heat it up.
I'm sorry, but I burned it.
Viewers.
Are you still there?
If you're there, come and chop some fishcakes.
(No response to the fishcakes)
(Mimi chops the fishcakes.)
It'll be ready in 1 minute 30 seconds.
(The head chef is making 3 pans of tteokbokki.)
I love you, customers.
- Will they be ready together?
- Yes.
That's great. This is it.
It's the last order, so I'm throwing in all the fried food.
Give them to me. I'll serve them all like this.
They aren't ready yet.
(Putting everything she's got)
- I'll serve the original.
- We can go together.
I need this.
- The food is ready.
- Can you top it with meat?
Excuse me. Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.
Here's your small original tteokbokki.
- Here you go.
- I'll take your glove.
(Serving the last tteokbokki)
(Humming)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
(Even the customer who came alone)
- This is good.
- Yes.
(Nodding with satisfaction)
Yes, sir.
I really love and respect you all.
Credit card, 40.5 dollars.
- Is the total correct?
- Yes.
It's easier to ask you.
The total is 28 dollars.
Fifty-dollar bill?
If you give me 50 dollars, how much do I owe you?
Twenty-two dollars. Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
(When the last customers leave, )
(it's finally a moment for them to catch their breath.)
The first day of Space Rice Cake's business is closed.
(It's their 2nd day.)
Thank you.
(Closed for business)
- Mimi, I'll do it.
- I just started.
Young Ji, you need to take a break.
Yu Jin, didn't we do really well today?
Were we fully booked the whole time?
I was too busy making tteokbokki...
to know what was going on.
Didn't we do very well?
(The head chef wants to know how big today's business was.)
It felt like it was twice as much as yesterday.
But in actual numbers, it must be 1.8 times as much.
How was the overall response to Broccolino Basiliano?
- People loved it.
- Did they?
Those who love creamy dishes went crazy for it.
Right?
How did you sell it so well?
The name is so difficult,
yet so many people ordered it.
What did you say to make them order it?
(Making a compliment)
It was all because of the food.
As expected,
you're Korea's number 1 salesperson and number 1 comedienne.
- And Baeksang Arts Awards winner.
- Nice.
She's soon to be an Oscar winner.
I already won the Baeksang Arts Award.
The Grammys, the Oscars,
and the Blue Dragon Film Awards are left.
Thank you.
- You'll win those awards soon.
- Thank you.
Start practicing your acceptance speech.
I don't know why my back hurts so much.
Have a seat. Let's stop for a second.
It's so exhausting...
Mimi, could you stop for a second?
It's so exhausting, but it's so much fun.
- Yes, it's fun.
- It's fun but it's exhausting.
(She's happy but exhausted.)
We need to take a break to keep running our business later.
- There's a lot of stuff.
- What?
Isn't it the crab cream croquette?
That's amazing.
- A croquette?
- It's available only in the summer.
- You can eat it only in the summer.
- Oh, my.
- We must eat it now.
- Yes, we do.
- Cheers.
(Clinking in a good mood)
It's so good.
There's crab meat inside.
- This feels like summer.
- Yes.
Eun Ji, these are churros.
Take a look at the churros.
(Mimi spots something sweet.)
I'll sprinkle it on.
(Lightly sprinkling powdered sugar)
(Shaking)
This is exactly what Mimi goes crazy for.
The caramel smell is insane.
(Humming)
It makes me feel so good.
There's cream.
(Caramel cream)
After taking a bite of this, Mimi came back.
It shooed away the jeolpyeon ghost.
Have some chicken with the sauce.
You're eating it without?
This is good.
(It hits her taste buds.)
- I feel so happy.
- Chicken drumstick.
It's so delicious.
(Summer snacks you must enjoy before summer ends)
(After the happy snack break)
Yes, this is good. Let's go.
It's not over yet.
I'm going to make cream bread.
Gosh, they look so cute.
They look exactly like Torong.
Mini gijeongtteok.
(Made by fermenting non-glutinous rice flour with makgeolli)
Didn't I leave...
a message to Producer Ye Seul?
(Some days before the opening of Space Rice Cake)
(Mimi proposed a dessert idea.)
(What if we cut grilled rice cake in half and fill it with cream?)
(That's a great idea. We'll fully support you.)
(The headquarters liked the idea...)
(and decided to provide gijeongtteok.)
In Bangkok,
there was something really interesting.
I was walking around, and I saw someone grill...
- bread on a gridiron.
- Bread?
Yes, bread.
They cut it in half, filled it with cream,
and served it like this as street food.
(Yaowarat toasted buns, Thai street dessert...)
(made with grilled bread filled with cream)
It was so good.
If we make it with rice cake, it'd work 100 percent.
(Cooking starts.)
This is very simple.
(Mimi reveals her signature rice cake dessert recipe.)
(First, brush melted butter onto a sheet of parchment paper.)
(Line up the gijeongtteok.)
(Brush each piece evenly with butter.)
These are all done.
(This helps make the outside crispy, the inside moist.)
Okay.
For ten minutes.
(Into the oven for an upgrade in texture and color)
(After a 10-minute tanning session)
They look done.
Mimi, the color looks so beautiful.
I want to try one.
- Aren't they pretty?
- They look delicious.
Ta-da.
Mimi, what is it called?
Cream rice cake.
(The baked gijeongtteok comes out fluffy.)
(Next is making the cream.)
I'll start with matcha.
Three tablespoons of matcha.
- Do I just stir it?
- Yes.
(A mascarpone-based cream...)
(paired with the bittersweet flavor of matcha)
(Next is the chocolate cream.)
One.
Mimi, it's going to be one incredible dessert.
Thank you.
(A sweet, delicious flavor that puts you in a good mood)
This is really...
Here you go. Try it.
How did you make this?
It's chocolate cream. I'm wondering if it should be richer than this.
I usually like it richer.
(Carefully)
- Gosh, it's good.
- Is it good enough?
- I want it to be richer.
- Really?
Add one more spoon. My taste is on the mild side.
- Gosh, it makes me feel good.
- It's delicious.
- You're good at making desserts.
This is definitely going to be delicious.
Here you go, Yu Jin.
(Tasting the chocolate cream again)
Yu Jin, tell her what you think.
(This time, it's the richer version of the chocolate cream.)
- It's good.
- Is it nice?
- Okay.
(Grinning from ear to ear)
It's good.
Split it in half like this.
(Once you cut open the browned rice cake to reveal the inside)
I'll squeeze this in between here.
Okay.
(Filling it generously with cream)
It'd be nice if we had a tray.
A tray?
To use it for what?
- Can you give me a sheet...
- Is this right?
Of parchment paper?
Mimi, you're a dessert master.
Thank you.
(Shall we try the matcha and chocolate cream rice cake?)
Try some of this, Young Ji.
(Eating)
Thank you.
See how it tastes.
Mimi, this is unbelievable.
- It tastes so good.
- Mimi.
How much should we sell this for? It's so good.
Wait, we have to sell this.
It's really good.
- Can you believe this?
- It's so good.
What should we do? Should we start selling it today?
- Maybe we can give it out...
- As an appetizer?
As an appetizer today.
If we're going to sell it officially, let's start tomorrow.
We'll give two per table.
Okay.
(30 minutes before opening)
(A final prep sprint)
Scissors.
(While the kitchen team is prepping the main dishes, )
(the dessert team starts prepping the new menu item.)
Split it in half.
(Taking it step by step like they were taught)
(Sawing through the gijeongtteok)
- Split it in half.
- Yes.
Cut it deep enough.
In the middle... My goodness.
(The opening is way too wide.)
(Feeling intimidated)
- Is it a failure?
- No.
- In the middle...
- This is okay for today.
It's okay if the cream sticks out.
There isn't enough cream.
(She tries her best.)
This one isn't quite right, is it?
(They just laugh nervously.)
It's an appetizer, so it's okay.
It's okay even if they don't look...
- pretty today.
- Okay.
I'll go and turn the sign.
(It's time to turn the sign around for business.)
Sticky rice cakes
Garaetteok
(Open for business)
Baekseoltteok
We're selling rice cakes.
Nice. We're starting.
Chef Kim Mi Hyun, honesty.
- Humility. Ahk.
- Ahk.
- I love you.
I love you.
(Meanwhile, the server is relaxed.)
(Strutting casually out the front door)
Everyone.
What brings you here?
(Appearing before the innocent little lambs)
(A scary older sister)
- Are there three of you?
- Yes.
Did you get permission...
- from your mom?
- Yes.
Why don't you introduce yourselves?
(They finish introducing themselves.)
Seo Hyun, Ji Woo, So Hyun.
Please come in.
Come all the way inside.
This is Space Rice Cake restaurant,
so you'll need to pay before you leave.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Take a seat at Table One.
- Take a look at the menu.
- Okay.
We have customers at Table One.
They're the cutest little girls in third grade.
- Three third-graders?
- Yes.
I told them, "We actually charge money here."
"Did you tell your moms that you were coming?"
They said, "Yes."
"Is that so?"
How did you talk to them?
"This is..."
(Intimidating)
This is insane.
(The little customers finally relax.)
There are photos up there.
- That's crazy.
- My gosh.
(Somewhat artificial-looking photos of them making rice cakes)
They have everything here.
It looks like they make rice cakes from scratch.
- That's so funny.
- Seo Hyun, Ji Woo, and So Hyun.
- They said our names.
(They suddenly get nervous again.)
- Did you look at the menu?
- Yes.
- May I take your order?
Okay.
Three original tteokbokki...
and one soda, please.
Okay.
Did you mean three small original tteokbokki?
A small for each of you?
Okay, I'll put in your order.
- Okay.
Am I scary when I talk?
- No.
- No, right?
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Will you buy...
- Get your money out.
- If you have one more bill...
- Okay.
This should be enough.
(They set it aside carefully.)
What do you think?
Give them a variety. This one is chocolate.
It's ready.
This is cream gijeongtteok.
We're trying to decide whether to make it a new menu item.
I'd love for you to try it...
and tell me what you think.
Your food will be ready soon.
(After explaining it at their eye level)
(Sneaking a little glance)
Her face is so small and pretty.
(They calm down and taste the cream rice cakes.)
- It's crispy.
- It's delicious.
Yes, it's crunchy.
- It could be a new menu item.
- I agree.
It tastes like butter tteok.
I can smell the butter.
I wonder why they don't sell it.
- This is really delicious.
- I know.
(Shy girls' table: 3 small original tteokbokki)
(1 soda)
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
Is this order correct?
Did they really make this order?
Each of them wants one small tteokbokki.
They're definitely MZers.
I think the three of them are pitching in.
- They're paying separately.
- Separately?
Is that right? I understand now.
(Getting ready to spring into action)
I'll do it all at once.
It's my first time getting three orders...
of the original tteokbokki.
I'll put all three in at exactly the same time.
They look cute. Did we make them today?
- Yes, they're freshly made.
- They look delicious.
It's ready.
(Adding 3 garaetteok at the same time)
(Serious)
(Mimi's frying factory is up and running.)
(A generous portion)
Gosh, it looks incredible.
They're going out at the same time.
We'll make sure that they stay friends.
- Let's go. Gosh.
- That's right.
This is great. Fast service is the best.
Your three orders of original tteokbokki are here.
The pot is extremely hot.
- The pot is very hot.
- Don't touch it.
Don't touch it.
We're off to a great start.
Why is it so calm? I like it.
Three orders of tteokbokki in seven minutes. How's that?
Three orders of tteokbokki in seven minutes?
That's insane.
Do you need help with anything?
Things are very calm for us now.
When ten people walk in,
things will be very different.
(Here's what she means by ten people.)
(After closing yesterday)
We already took our last order.
- I'll make a reservation for you.
- Thank you.
(Setting up the reserved tables in advance)
Then we'll do it like this.
We're expecting ten people.
- Right.
- I think they're coming now.
Here comes the mini-van.
Are they here yet?
(Space Rice Cake)
(An enormous parade of customers)
(Walking in with confidence)
They're coming.
They're coming, right?
Gosh, they're here.
- Hello.
There are ten of us.
- Please come this way.
- The ten who made a reservation.
We marked the reserved tables for you.
Thank you.
Head chef, are you ready?
Honestly, I'm not ready.
But it has nothing to do with how prepared I am.
(It looks like the Last Supper.)
You don't want it?
- We should try everything.
- Right.
We need to try everything.
Besides, we eat a lot.
We must order a lot.
- We should order the desserts now.
- Right.
- We must order everything at once.
- Mom, can I get a slushy?
I'm expecting the group of five to order...
- an insane amount of food.
- Okay.
- We'd like to order.
(Finally, it's the moment of truth.)
I expect three orders of medium.
Or it could be four orders.
(Feeling empty)
Four orders of medium?
- Are you sure? Not a medium?
- Okay.
- Do we have to order one...
- Yes?
Jade Emperor Tteokbokki per person?
- Isn't it per person?
- Is it one order per person?
The Jade Emperor challenge is available...
for up to four people.
- Then let's order just 1.
- Just 1.
Just one? Okay.
I'll put in this order.
(The biggest group ever makes the head chef nervous.)
May I start reading the order?
I'm ready.
Two medium...
- original tteokbokki.
- Okay.
One medium...
- ghost pepper tteokbokki.
- Okay.
One order...
- of Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.
- Okay.
Two orders of pollack roe and clam pasta.
(Large group table's order)
Two orders of small Broccolino Basiliano.
Eight pomegranate slushies.
Three coffee slushies.
And ten orders of tiramisu.
What should we send out first?
- We can do it, head chef.
- We can do this.
(Order Status for the service team)
(Tteokramisu chestnut, coffee slushy, pomegranate slushy)
(8 dishes, 10 desserts, 11 drinks)
(A total order of 29 items)
(She tries to stay calm.)
Hold on, what was it again?
(Just then, more customers arrive.)
Welcome. How many are you?
Three more elementary school kids just came in.
- What kind of customers?
- Elementary school kids...
- Elementary school kids?
- as customers.
One small original tteokbokki,
one small ghost pepper tteokbokki,
and two sodas.
- Is that from another table?
- Yes, it is.
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(Small original tteokbokki, small mala tteokbokki)
(There are 6 orders of tteokbokki for the large group, )
(but there are only 3 burners.)
Here's my plan.
(That's when Young Ji comes up with a brilliant idea.)
We'll serve one small original tteokbokki,
Broccolino Basiliano, and the challenge together.
After that, we'll serve one original for the other table.
(Jade Emperor, small Basiliano, small original tteokbokki)
(Basiliano and Jade Emperor for the large group)
(Small original tteokbokki for the elementary school kids)
(She plans to make them at the same time.)
Don't panic, Young Ji.
- You can do it, chef.
- Young Ji, you can do it.
Chef, you can do it.
You're the one who just used all three burners at once.
Yes, I can do this.
(She turns on all three burners again.)
(Dropping garaetteok into the original and basil tteokbokki)
(Next up, it's Jade Emperor Tteokbokki.)
(2 tablespoons of chili bean sauce)
(1 teaspoon of ghost pepper powder)
(3 tablespoons of Sichuan pepper oil)
(Adding a 175cm-long whole garaetteok)
(All she has to do is wait for the sauce to reduce.)
Yu Jin, we have so many desserts to make.
- One small tteokbokki.
- I know.
- For the pomegranate slushy...
- There are ten tiramisus?
How many pomegranate slushies are there?
Five, six, seven, eight.
- Are there ten tiramisus?
- Yes.
- I'll start making the tiramisu.
- Okay.
(She plans to make half of it in advance.)
I'll take care of the drinks.
- Thank you.
- Yu Jin, you take care of desserts.
I can totally count on you, Eun Ji.
We're one.
We're definitely one.
I'll start by serving the appetizers.
(Serving the cream rice cakes first)
At Space Rice Cake fine dining,
we're developing a new menu item.
I brought some in case you'd like to try it.
- Thank you.
(Immediately after, )
(she starts making slushies.)
(One drink is ready.)
(It's endless no matter how much she makes.)
(The never-ending slushy cycle)
(Serving while making it obvious that she's struggling)
Stay in your seats. I got this.
(Yu Jin is in charge of the tteokramisu chestnut.)
(There's no end no matter how many she stacks up.)
(The never-ending tteokramisu chestnut cycle)
(Storing five of them in the fridge for now)
If you don't mind,
our pastry chef would like to hear...
what you thought of the rice cakes.
- They're delicious.
- The two of them tried.
- Did you like them?
- Yes.
Do you think it would be better with more cream?
- The amount was perfect.
- It was perfect?
How was the amount of cream at that table?
- It was good enough.
- It was good enough?
- Okay. Thank you, everyone.
- Sure.
They said the cream rice cake was really delicious,
the amount of cream was just right,
and they liked how sweet the cream was.
Nice.
We should go for it.
Mi Hyun, let's make it an official menu item.
- Thank you.
- You're amazing.
(It passed the customer taste test.)
- Is it the challenge first?
- Yes, it is.
But the elementary school kids are waiting for the original tteokbokki.
I made their small original tteokbokki first.
I also prepared Broccolino Basiliano.
(What is she saying?)
It's okay.
I don't understand what you mean.
She made dishes for the reserved group and the other table.
- Is that what she means?
- Yes.
(Thinking)
Do you want me to stir-fry the beef loin?
- We're out of burners.
- Is that so?
Should I bring out the portable burner and do it?
That would be amazing.
I'll bring out the portable burner and cook the beef loin.
I was going to prep the beef loin, but we don’t have a burner.
Does anyone have one?
(It's complete chaos.)
If you cook all of that, Young Ji will use it.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
(While Eun Ji is stir-frying the beef loin)
Small Basiliano is ready.
Who ordered the basil tteokbokki?
A small original tteokbokki is ready.
Make sure not to touch it.
(Serving the elementary school kids)
(And pollack roe and clam pasta is ready.)
- Be careful. It's hot.
- Okay.
(Serving the large group)
Enjoy your food.
- The challenge is ready.
- Okay.
(Enjoy your food until Jade Emperor Tteokbokki is served.)
- Ghost pepper tteokbokki is ready.
- Okay.
Young Ji, you can use all the fried food on the right.
- It's big today.
- Okay.
(Piling on a generous amount of fried toppings)
(And topping it off with beef loin)
(She sprinkles some Cheongyang chili pepper on top.)
(And...)
(squeezing in a generous amount of capsaicin sauce)
(It's a much more intense version of the challenge.)
- The challenge dish is ready.
- Could you put it up here?
- I'd appreciate it.
- It's terrifying today.
- Thank you.
- Warn them that it's very spicy.
- Nice.
The four of you...
taking on the Jade Emperor Tteokbokki challenge.
Please leave it here.
Head Chef Lee Young Ji came fully prepared...
- for today.
- That wasn't necessary.
(1 Jade Emperor Tteokbokki)
Thank you.
- Finish it with a sense of duty.
- Please take lots of fun photos.
Did the first group of customers fail?
- They made it.
- Did anyone make it?
- They made it?
Doesn't that mean that it's possible?
Our head chef was angry...
about their success.
So the difficulty level might have gone up...
- a little.
- This is going to kill us.
I'll be lenient since it's the first day.
(Version 1 for yesterday's challenge)
(Version 2 for today's challenge)
The food challenge gets spicier than before...
so that no one can succeed.
We'll start.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Ready, set, go.
You can do it.
(Bravely taking the first bite)
It looks spicy.
- Is it very spicy?
- Please enjoy.
Hang in there. You can do it.
- The flavor hits you at once.
- Hang in there.
- Is it like mala sauce?
- Yes.
- Does it taste like mala?
- Spicy mala can be very spicy.
(We thought that he was perfectly calm.)
Give me some tissue.
- Isn't it spicy? Don't you feel it?
- It's spicy.
(They can't think straight.)
Can you read the remaining orders for me?
Two medium original tteokbokki.
(1 medium mala tteokbokki, 1 small basil tteokbokki for the group)
(1 small mala tteokbokki for the elementary school kids)
Thank you.
Two small and three medium.
(Yu Jin goes to stir-fry the beef loin.)
- Is there any priority order?
- Did you say beef loin?
I'm stir-frying it now.
I meant priority order, not beef loin.
I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
- Priority order? I see.
(Absolute chaos)
(Remaining Order Status)
(Meanwhile, Mimi makes another pollack roe and clam pasta.)
If the pasta is ready, may I decorate it and serve it?
(Finishing it up for the busy chef)
Here's one more dish for you.
It's hot. Hold it by the top.
Mimi, all your pasta orders are out.
I'm done.
(Mimi's orders are done.)
(And one person still has a long way to go.)
(Medium original, medium mala, small basil for the large group)
(There are rice cakes.)
(There are no rice cakes for the other two.)
(A long way off)
(Customers show up at the worst possible moment.)
Hello. Welcome.
- How many are you?
- We're two.
Two? Please go inside.
I'll put in the order. Thank you.
(Two friends' table: 1 small original tteokbokki...)
I'll read the order.
(Remaining Order Status)
- Small Broccolino is ready.
- Okay.
(Totally exhausted)
- It's been four minutes.
- Are you okay?
Do you want this?
- You can do it - You can do it.
(The kids start cheering them on.)
(The dads keep fighting their way through it.)
(The pot is starting to show the bottom.)
Success!
Did we get the wrong flavor or something?
- Was it not spicy?
- It was sweet.
It was sweet?
(He's just showing off.)
We'll test it.
Everyone, scream!
I think they completed the challenge.
- The challenge?
(But it wasn't bad news only for Young Ji.)
Yes, they completed it successfully.
Where's my slushy? Is this it?
(They ran out of their slushies due to the challenge.)
Nine pomegranate slushies, please.
Nine on top of eight pomegranate slushies that you ordered?
I feel great.
- We met the Jade Emperor.
- That's why you crave some more.
(There isn't much left.)
(The slushy factory is back on.)
(She makes as many as possible.)
We're in trouble. We ran out of slushies.
I need to tell them...
that our pomegranate slushies are sold out.
Unfortunately, our pomegranate slushies are sold out.
- You should share them.
- I'll serve you only five.
- Okay. Thank you.
- I'm very sorry.
This isn't exactly fine dining, is it? I'm sorry, everyone.
Yu Jin, pomegranate slushies are sold out. Don't take more orders.
They're sold out for now.
- When they're ready...
- We'll sell them again.
(She runs to refill the slushy.)
- Medium original is ready.
- Okay.
(Frantically sending out dishes)
Original tteokbokki is your last one. Shall I serve on this side?
Is this our last dish?
Yes, and you have desserts coming up.
- By the way...
- That's right.
Earlier, you ordered ten.
How full are you now? If you're too full...
- I'm not full.
- You aren't?
(Of course not)
- Really? Shall I bring ten?
- Yes.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
(Eun Ji will make tteokramisu chestnut.)
Tteokramisu chestnut!
Gosh, my back is killing me.
(Even though she's letting out groans of pain)
(She got the hang of piping the chestnut cream.)
This is insane. I'm getting so good at it.
(After all that intensive training)
(Plenty of them are ready to go.)
I'm getting better and better.
(A lot of self-praising)
- You're doing well.
- Be careful.
- Ten tteokramisu?
- Ten tteokramisu are coming out.
- That's amazing.
- Here are your desserts.
- They're here.
It's tteokramisu.
- It looks so good.
- Thank you.
- I'll serve you.
- Thank you so much.
Enjoy your dessert. Thank you.
(After overcoming the biggest hurdle)
Well done, everyone.
Serving ten tiramisus was impressive.
Yu Jin made them all in advance.
I love you.
I love you so much.
- I love you a lot today.
- I love you so much.
Small ghost pepper tteokbokki is ready.
Broccolino Basiliano is done.
- Yu Jin, small original is ready.
- Okay.
(Remaining Order Status)
(Mimi double-checks the orders for Young Ji.)
One small original tteokbokki.
There's still pollack roe and clam pasta.
Was there one pollack roe and clam pasta?
- Yes, at Table Four.
- Okay.
I must've missed it.
(When they were tackling the big group order)
I'll read the order.
Give it to me. Leave it there.
One small original tteokbokki.
One pollack roe and clam pasta.
- Black pepper?
- Yes, thank you.
Pomegranate slushies.
(She forgot about her own order while taking care of the head chef.)
(That was a close call.)
Gosh, I didn't hear anything.
I figured out the quickest way to make it.
- You can do it.
- I can do it.
(She jumps straight into cooking.)
(Drizzling in a generous amount of olive oil)
(Tossing in garlic and crushed red pepper)
It's nice and spicy.
(She smiles first even though she's in a hurry.)
(Your food will be ready soon.)
I feel like I'm not...
- in this world anymore.
- Me too.
Go.
(She uses the wok from out of this world.)
You're doing so well.
(Mimi's rock star cooking comes to an end.)
- Ta-da.
- It looks beautiful.
(We'll serve it right away.)
(The next customer toddles in.)
What's this?
- This is...
- Is that the menu?
So cute.
- Mommy, I want food.
- What shall we eat?
(Yu Jin goes to take the order.)
Would you like to order? Hello.
Hi.
- One tteokramisu chestnut...
- Yes.
- and that broccoli dish.
- Okay.
(As soon as she's done taking the orders, )
(a new group of customers enter.)
- Small.
- One small.
Basil... Broccolino Basiliano...
I'm asking just in case.
You ordered two small and one medium.
It might be quite a lot.
- Will it be okay?
- We're very hungry.
We take some time to prepare.
We'll try to be as fast as we can.
(Yet again...)
Dongchimi...
(Space Rice Cake is full.)
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(2 small basil, 1 small original, 1 medium mala)
One small original, one medium ghost pepper.
And there's one small broccoli.
Fourteen. All tteokramisu chestnuts are done!
(Young Ji's burners are full.)
Take it slow.
Everyone is enjoying themselves. Take it slow.
(It's time for the appetizer.)
Hello, my apologies for the late greeting.
I'm sorry.
We wanted to run it...
like fine dining,
but it wasn't easy to do so.
I'm sorry, dear customers.
- Here is cream gijeongtteok.
- Thank you.
- Say thank you.
(Falling to her knees)
I'm so happy.
Say "I love you."
I love you.
(Shouting)
(Dizzy)
How did you do that, Prince?
Enjoy your food.
I'm glad we're doing cream gijeongtteok.
We can buy time.
We can buy time by giving them cream gijeongtteok...
and let them enjoy it.
What rice cake is this?
It's delicious.
It's good, right?
(While cream gijeongtteok gave the kitchen a breather...)
It's turned off again.
I'll kill you.
This is so hard.
(The only thing that gives strength to Young Ji...)
(who's having a hard time)
I freshly made it, so use it as is.
Okay, thank you.
- Can the broccoli be served?
- Yes, it can.
(Her ever-so-reliable right-hand chef)
Thank you.
- It's pretty.
- Thank you.
(Chef Mimi's task: Compliment when needed)
(When the head chef sprinkles pepper...)
Nice, this is the last one.
Thank you.
There's one more small broccoli,
- right?
- That's right, small size.
(Chef Mimi's task: Check the remaining orders)
- Small broccoli is ready.
- Thank you.
Here is broccoli small size.
And here.
- And here's the kids' cutlery...
- Auntie.
- Yes.
- Sister.
Call her sister.
- Am I a sister?
Say thank you.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
- Is it tteokbokki?
- It is.
I want to eat tteokbokki.
Do you want to eat tteokbokki?
(Taking a big bite)
(The young boy is satisfied too.)
(The kitchen, which has finished sending out a load of orders...)
We can do this.
Should I wash the pots for you first?
- Yes.
- Wash the pots first?
Yes. Thank you, service team.
I'm indebted to you.
(However)
(The debt keeps piling up...)
- This is...
- It's okay.
Leave them here.
I'll just wash this real quick.
And Yu Jin, in front of the gate,
there's a queue...
(The debt keeps piling up...)
- This is...
- It's okay.
Leave them here.
I'll just wash this real quick.
And Yu Jin, in front of the gate,
there's a queue, I think.
You should check.
(That's not true.)
(Still, she greets them with professionalism.)
- Hello.
How many of you?
- We're... Three, yes.
- Three?
- And one baby.
- One baby.
(Customers are waiting outside.)
(Plates are waiting on the sink.)
Producer Na, help us do the dishes.
I'll go and help if you ask more desperately.
Please!
Who am I?
- What?
- Who am I?
A middle-aged man in Korea.
A middle-aged man in Korea...
who dominates many broadcasting stations.
The greatest middle-aged man in Korea.
Please pick up from here.
Who summoned the middle-aged man in Korea?
The coolest middle-aged man in Korea.
(Buttering him up without looking)
(He throws away the leftovers with practiced ease.)
Producer Na is doing it.
(The middle-aged man puts it into the dishwasher.)
Thank you, middle-aged man in Korea.
Medium ghost pepper...
- Medium size.
- is ready.
But there's no server, is there?
Ghost pepper medium is served.
Coming.
(Running to the kitchen)
I need to serve one soft drink too.
Soft drink.
- Ghost pepper medium, right?
- That's right.
(The floor is hectic today.)
Yes.
Be careful. Should I change it?
- Yes.
- We'll eat...
- Thank you.
- Don't hesitate.
(The hungry table: 3 original tteokbokki)
Here's your basil tteokbokki too.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
(Tteokbokki Order Status: All complete)
Shall we pay together?
- Yes, let's go.
- Let's go.
Yu Jin, we need to clean the big table together.
We can bring them in now. The big group is leaving.
(The service team is coming.)
Yu Jin, join me after they pay.
Ms. Lee, I apologize.
- Please come inside.
- Okay.
But we've yet to clean the table.
If you'd sit by the side...
Please wait here. We'll clean quickly.
Please sit down.
(She quickly starts to clean.)
I'm very sorry.
Although we're a fine-dining restaurant...
(Her obsession with premiumization continues.)
- Say hello.
- This is really hard.
The situation is...
- The kitchen is total chaos.
- Really?
(The yard is too.)
- Do you accept cards?
- Yes.
I need to calculate manually, so it takes time.
Don't worry about it.
- Original tteokbokki...
- It was a lot.
It's medium.
(The first bulk calculation got her a bit flustered.)
Original tteokbokki medium.
Jade Emperor Tteokbokki. You've succeeded the challenge,
so this is free.
So...
The pomegranate...
We'll calculate it and come back.
I'll do it here.
- You can go. You must be busy.
- Thank you and sorry.
Let's calculate.
Come here.
(She volunteers to calculate for the panicked staff.)
- Here.
- Ji Ho.
I'm really sorry.
Say hi to her.
(Yu Jin quickly joins Eun Ji.)
- I'll go and come back.
- Thank you.
I haven't finished calculating.
- Go and do that first.
- Okay.
I think we need to invite part-timers...
from Seoul.
Please think about who'd make a good part-timer.
(We should think about it?)
Excuse me. Thank you.
- It's 198 dollars.
- Is it 198 dollars?
Thank you.
(Double-checking is a luxury.)
Please sign here.
- I'm so sorry.
- You worked hard.
This is our first time having a big group of customers.
(Regretful)
Thank you so much for enjoying the food.
- Thank you.
- One, two, three.
(They take a photo to celebrate the success of the challenge.)
Thank you, dear customers.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Bye.
(It looks like they'll catch a breather.)
(But another group is waiting outside.)
We haven't even cleared the table.
(Current time: 7:26pm)
We haven't even...
Call a part-timer.
We're nearing the last order. Hang in there.
Let's do this.
It's the last order?
The business isn't closed, though.
Please come inside.
(More customers are coming.)
- Are you okay with outdoors?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
(The traces of the big group still remain.)
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry. I'll come back and clean it up quickly.
- Okay. Come here, Seo A.
- I'll be quick.
(Rushing)
Who can help us clear the big table? Nobody.
I can help you now.
- Hello.
- Please clean the outdoor table...
all the way to the end.
(I'm coming.)
- Where...
- Did the head chef...
- go?
- Yes.
- Hello.
- These are the leftovers.
- Yes.
Such a hideous sight.
I'm so sorry.
You should bring a tray too.
I work in the kitchen, you see.
- I need a tray.
- You startled me.
(A human rocket)
She sure is rowdy.
There's the menu.
(Total chaos)
I'm sorry.
- While we wipe the tables...
- Hello.
- Thank you so much for helping.
- You're so pretty.
Thank you.
I make mean tteokbokki.
I hope you enjoy tteokbokki.
- May I explain the drinks?
- Hello.
It'll take less than a minute.
(They finish cleaning up the table.)
This is my guess.
(Land)
Two small, one medium.
- I trust your gut feeling.
- Yes.
There'll definitely be 1 medium, and definitely 2 small.
I'm sure.
If I'm wrong,
I'll take off my pants here.
Why'd you take off your pants?
Please don't do that.
Here's the order.
For Table Five,
One small original tteokbokki.
One small ghost pepper,
one pollack roe and clam pasta,
one small broccoli.
(Table 3-generation family)
Is that all?
(You wish.)
Small original, small ghost pepper,
one pollack roe and clam pasta, and one small broccoli.
One more of this set? Okay.
Pomegranate and coffee slushies too.
(Tteokbokki Order Status)
(2 small basil, 2 small original, 2 small mala)
Let's go, Lee Young Ji. You can do this.
(And Mimi is flustered by pollack roe and clam pasta.)
I put the pasta away thinking it was over.
(Crying)
There was one last one.
This is really the last one.
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
It starts now.
- Not start.
- What do you mean?
I need one more small plate.
- Producer Na, a small plate.
- Small plate.
You can do it.
Please say an encouragement to the middle-aged man.
Middle-aged man, you can do it!
You can do it!
Thank you.
I like the energy.
(Young Ji uses all three burners with energy.)
- Broccoli is ready.
- Okay.
- Original is complete.
Here is original tteokbokki.
Thank you.
Yours will be served in 30 seconds.
- Us?
- Please wait.
A small original.
Your tteokbokki is here.
- This.
- My gosh.
They were waiting for too long,
so I served them pasta first.
- They got their pasta.
- Okay.
The rest are the same.
I'll sort it out and let you know.
Okay.
Try this.
Cut some for me.
Original tteokbokki is really good.
Did they learn the recipe from a chef?
I'm sure they did.
- It's so good.
- Right?
It's good, right?
A small ghost pepper.
Broccoli small is complete.
- Here comes the original.
- Okay.
(1 small mala left)
(Meanwhile, the customers indoors are ready to leave.)
I finished eating.
(I finished eating!)
Bye.
- Bye.
- Cute.
I'll help you with the bill.
(Cleaning again)
(And a talent show)
I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for the food...
Thank you for the food.
(She must be very tired.)
Why did you say that?
Today's last tteokbokki.
I'll deep-fry them now.
It has a lot of meat.
How generous for the last plate.
(The last tteokbokki has a generous amount of toppings.)
Today's last tteokbokki.
The baby can't have this. It's very spicy.
This is my favorite.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Thankfully, the reviews are positive.)
This is good too.
One soft drink.
That's 49.4 dollars.
- Have a safe trip back.
- Thank you.
- Go back safely.
I hope they liked it.
Are we the only ones left?
Take your time.
- How's the taste?
- This is my favorite.
- As long as it tastes good...
- It's good.
How's the basil?
The rice cake itself is good.
Is that so? We made it ourselves.
- Really?
- In the morning...
We woke up at 6am and made it ourselves.
(The owner, who's done cooking, helps to clean.)
Eat as slowly as you can.
(Slightly uncomfortable)
I'm not that kind of person. Please take it slow.
- Eat quickly.
Mr. Part-timer.
(And...)
- Mr. Part-timer, come here.
- Okay.
I'm not done with my work.
- Thank you so much.
- But...
You can go home now.
- Guys, Mr. Part-timer...
- Thank you so much.
His clothes are wet too.
(Looking messy)
Thank you, ahk.
- Ahk.
Fresh cream runs out quickly.
They love cream gijeongtteok.
Can we, a bit...
When the last customers pay, can we...
Shall we go and greet them together?
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
Don't feel sorry when you ask for something!
Be confident!
Don't feel sorry when it's us.
- That's not how we roll.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Don't be sorry.
- Let's greet them together.
(The last customers get up at that time.)
- How was it?
- It's good.
- Is it good?
- Did you like it?
- I'm glad.
- Come again.
- We do it for ten days.
- One small...
Go back safely.
Bye.
- Bye, thank you.
- Bye.
(Today's last customers leave.)
(Current time: 8:33pm)
(The 2nd day business ends!)
Closed.
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
I think we made 1,000 dollars today.
First of all, everyone worked so hard.
- This is impossible.
- Good job, guys.
That was the best.
With the best teammates.
It's incredible.
Shall we see how hard we've worked...
- by checking the sales?
- Okay.
You got 30 dollars cash?
It's 29 dollars.
If I add 29 dollars,
it's 800 dollars.
- The total sales?
- Yes.
- It's almost 1,000 dollars.
- It's 800 dollars.
(It's almost 1,000 dollars!)
(Card payment: 805.70 dollars, Cash payment: 57 dollars)
(Calculation mistake: 29.80 dollars)
(Total: 832.90 dollars)
(But...)
- I have a question.
- Yes.
The middle-aged man we hired for just a while.
What's his hourly wage?
- The minimum wage...
- Yes.
Is 10.32 dollars.
- He worked for 30 minutes.
- But...
- it was late.
- Like... Yes.
- He worked overtime.
- Overtime pay.
So it's supposed to be 16 dollars. How long did he work?
Hold on, 16 dollars is...
the price of one Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki.
Didn't you earn more than 800 dollars today?
But we...
But he was pretty efficient.
- He really was a big help.
- He was efficient.
As long as Yeong Seok doesn't get a lot.
Then if we maintain...
a good relationship with the middle-aged man,
pay him well and such.
- Can we work tomorrow too?
- Of course.
- Really?
- During busy hours.
(Negotiation complete)
(1 Yeong Seok equals 1 mala tteokbokki.)
When ten tteokramisu chestnuts were served,
- I felt ecstatic.
- I know what you mean.
I was so surprised with how fast Yu Jin was.
Young Ji got the hang of it too.
- A cash register would be nice.
- About 100 dollars.
So this was what happened.
I had to calculate...
for ten people.
My hands started to tremble.
- Of course.
- "How do I handle this?"
The bill was super long, like ten items on it.
I came halfway.
I was supposed to type 16 dollars,
but I typed 160 dollars instead.
She was like, "We'll do it."
So I was like, "It's okay. Wait, where was I calculating?"
Okay.
Everything else is fine, but a cash register.
We accept real money,
- so when you calculate it, - Exactly.
- you'll feel nervous.
- It's pressuring.
- It's so pressuring.
- They said they'd do it,
and I hate myself for thinking they might've calculated...
a bit less.
The customer who ate Jade Emperor Tteokbokki said,
"It's sweet."
She's insulted again.
Really? We keep giving away free 40-dollar dishes.
Exactly.
It's better than them feeling ill afterwards.
But we can take a one-day break.
Yes, we should.
I have a list of city tour...
- that I want to do with you.
- There are so many things to do.
- It's so nice.
- The general store?
We must go to the general store.
Are we doing a city tour on the day off?
We need to go to Hanaro Mart too.
And we should take photos in the photo studio too.
- Like family portrait?
- When we're in good condition.
I want to take one when we're in good condition.
So I miss the times...
when you guys could dance and have fun...
without a care in the world.
I'm thinking if I ever had that time.
(It feels like her previous life.)
I felt it as I was making tteokbokki.
"I think I've lived 20 years doing this."
I'm really curious about the general store.
- The general store.
- We didn't get to go.
It sounds like paradise.
(The rumored place of wonders)
"Have you been to paradise?"
"Have you seen the blue sky?"
"Have you seen the blue country?"
(Have you seen the blue sky)
- "Have you seen the blue country?"
- Mimi.
You always come back from the general store like this.
"You know, the general store has..."
"this and that."
All we do is...
(Exclaiming)
We went to the general store today...
You must check it out when the show airs.
All we could think about were you two.
"I'll buy the boots for Young Ji."
- "This is perfect for Mimi."
- I thought so too.
We did all sorts of things.
And just for buying one gimbap,
- I...
- I didn't expect...
- to be criticized so badly.
- One gimbap.
- I had a reason.
- I never imagined.
- But I understand why you did that.
- Right before you came,
Producer Ye Seul came to me, and with her signature tone said,
"Young Ji, I have something to tell you."
"How much did you sell yesterday?"
It was 400 dollars.
"They spent 300 dollars on grocery shopping."
- She provoked you.
- She provoked me.
We came right after that, didn't we?
You did, with gimbap.
It's her scheme.
- She provoked you on purpose.
- She did that on purpose.
You fell for it.
- You fell for it.
- I've been on many survival shows,
- but I failed to recognize it.
- You didn't know.
In the end, I ate most of the gimbap.
I'm so sorry.
You and Mimi kept refusing to eat,
saying you didn't have an appetite.
So I thought you should have a proper lunch at least.
We had a time limit,
but we ran and got it somehow.
We ran to buy that gimbap.
- You...
- Yes.
Hold on.
Are you serious? What's wrong with her?
(Fidgety)
- This is so funny.
- Was it that sad?
- Are you two dating?
I'm sorry, Yu Jin.
I totally get it.
- If you watch what happened before.
- Were you that upset?
I wasn't upset.
It's not because of you.
She can't sleep at night if I leave it at this.
- It's not because of you.
- So...
I shed a tear...
- while laughing.
- Because it's funny.
I was so upset, but I held it in.
"She must be sensitive now."
(Holding back her tears)
I held it in and went to a corner.
During that time, I turned around like this...
to avoid the camera.
(She has nothing to say.)
(The story Young Ji didn't know)
- Is there anything you want to eat?
- What about you, Mimi?
- If you're hungry.
- Not really.
Okay.
- We'll just have the basil dish.
- Okay.
(Since this morning, the youngest one has been...)
- I should get them vitamins.
- Make them have some.
I should get Mimi chocolates today. Did she have any yesterday?
Mimi had some chocolates before she left for work today.
And I gave her a piece of chocolate I brought from the US.
Let's limit our spending today.
- We shouldn't hurt our sales.
- That's right.
(Because their sales were humble, )
- We didn't spend much today.
- Thank you.
(they didn't have money.)
Run, Eun Ji. We don't have time. Hop in.
(They didn't have much time either.)
- The kitchen team needs it.
- We should get what they need.
(She was determined to do so.)
(How much did you spend on groceries today?)
(We spent 13.5 dollars to buy gimbap.)
- we spent 13.5 dollars.
- Gimbap?
- We bought gimbap.
- It's for our lunch.
(Young Ji, who didn't know, was more worried about money.)
Didn't you say you'd ask before you buy something?
(Yu Jin was flustered.)
If you yell at me for spending 13.5 dollars for lunch...
(They were hurt, but they kept it to themselves.)
I'm not yelling at you. We didn't even set a budget.
Young Ji must've felt sorry. She approached me like this.
- She suddenly said, - Let's stop eating.
"Hey, let me see your notepad."
- It was out of the blue.
- Are you high school students?
- Are you?
- "Hey, let me see your notepad."
- How cute.
- It’s amazing...
how accurately she remembers it.
- It's like an all-boys high school.
- It gets funnier.
I realized that was her way of making amends.
While thinking it was funny, I went, "Here."
- Did you?
- And...
she flipped the pages and went, "Gosh."
"Let's have some gimbap."
"Hey, let's have some gimbap."
That's a strange way to make amends.
Hey. Are you two going out or what?
- She was embarrassed.
- Why do you eat...
with your head down?
Look up and eat.
Why do you eat chicken with your head down?
Are you ashamed right now?
Hey, hold on. It's because...
I feel like this part will be aired.
(Correct.)
Keep going.
- You have your side of the story.
- Keep going.
- I'll let you tell it later.
- I don't have much to say.
"Hey, let's have some gimbap."
She said that, and I followed her.
While eating gimbap, I got over it already.
It wasn't worth getting upset about. While eating gimbap, I said,
"Yes, Young Ji. I'm glad you're enjoying gimbap."
"Have some more." And I wasn't upset anymore.
Do you know what's funny?
I was pissed at one point because I was anxious.
Maybe I really thought we could make 100,000 dollars.
So, I was anxious.
Then I had these flashbacks.
Come to think of it, Yu Jin bought a squishy toy, yogurt,
and snacks yesterday. I remembered them all.
I thought, "She wasted money."
The moment I lashed out, I had another flashback.
What was the flashback about?
Yu Jin punching numbers into a calculator...
to buy stuff with a discount.
- I was really worried about her.
- Okay.
She was anxious even before we left.
I've never seen her this anxious in person.
- Right.
- So,
like her manager,
- I wanted to take good care of her.
- That's right.
While talking about the flashback,
I remembered how I was, and I was suddenly...
(Choked up)
I thought, "Yes, I cared about her to this extent."
I had flashbacks.
(She has nothing to say.)
That was before. I'm not upset at all now.
- You don't feel upset.
- We made amends.
- I understand her completely.
- Sit straight.
I was very surprised just now.
She loves me a lot.
- What's with you?
- It's a kind of agape love.
- It's not. Don't take it too far.
- Is that so?
I'm really concerned about you. And I keep thinking about you.
- It's ape love...
- What's agape love?
- I don't really know.
- Why did you pretend to know it?
- It's because...
Yu Jin didn't love me this much during Season 1 and 2.
But I could suddenly feel how deeply she cared for me.
I felt like I'm So Ji Sub...
- from "I'm Sorry, I Love You."
- Like Moo Hyeok?
And she's Song Eun Chae.
When I saw her cry, she resembled Eun Chae a bit.
Gosh.
- Stop shooting a drama.
- We're done.
Hey, doesn't it feel great...
- to have sweats after work?
- It does.
- I'll have my favorite ice cream.
- Me too.
- I love it.
- Is this your favorite?
- Nice.
- This is the original one.
- The original one is delicious too.
- I'll have the corn flavor.
I got the new flavor.
- I got salted milk and caramel.
- It's salted milk and caramel.
- Thank you.
- It looks good.
This is...
(Savoring)
It's salted milk ice cream with caramel.
- You'd love it, Mimi.
- It must be so soft.
Try it. It's really good.
- It's something you'd love.
- It's so tasty.
(Amazed)
- Is it good?
- It's good. Try it.
Sticky rice cake goes well with ice cream.
- It's good.
- It's really tasty, Eun Ji.
- We can make a dessert like this.
- Sounds good.
- It's so good.
- I like the idea.
Let's copy it.
Don't you think the rice cake has gotten softer?
Everyone loves this one. You can't go wrong with this.
Can't we develop a new menu...
by putting ice cream and rice cake together?
- Sounds good.
- Yes. I think it's a good idea.
I love it.
(At their accommodations after work)
(Beeping)
Someone's here.
Who is it?
- An intruder.
You got ready for bed real fast.
- We were just chatting?
- Really?
I'm here to borrow your foam roller.
We talked about this earlier, but Eun Ji and I...
(Chit-chatting while she's here)
- It's hard to jot down the orders.
- It is.
It's so hard.
The names are like Don't Eat Ghost Pepper Tteokbokki...
- I tried to shorten it.
- Okay.
Without talking to everyone beforehand,
I just wrote "Mala," and it created confusion.
So before we start tomorrow,
we should figure out ways to simplify the dish names.
(The sales talk continues even after work.)
- That would be great.
- The best way is...
It should be easy to hear for Young Ji.
It's simple for me because it's pollack roe and clams.
- You can call it whatever.
- Yes.
For Young Ji, let's go with the original,
the mala,
- And basil.
- and the basil.
If you keep it simple like that,
it would be the best.
And it's easier for us too.
- It's easier to write and read.
- It's easier to write down.
You wrote the whole name for the ghost pepper tteokbokki.
And that one and broccoli are confusing too.
Exactly. You wrote the whole name down.
- But...
- You wrote down broccoli too.
But when we shortened it and didn't write the whole name,
- since we scribbled, - It's confusing.
The names were confusing.
- You're here.
- What is this?
(Young Ji joins them.)
- You didn't take a shower.
- No.
- You didn't take a shower?
- No. I'm going to wash up now.
- What did you do, then?
- I was taking it easy.
- You watched something, right?
Take a shower first, Young Ji.
Let's keep the names as Basil and Mala between us.
- That sounds great.
- On the order sheets.
- We should say Basil and Mala.
- Yes. We'll do that tomorrow.
(They agreed to shorten the names.)
(The 2nd day of business drew to a close.)
(Morning has come to Space Rice Cake.)
- Hello.
- Good morning.
- Chang Dae.
- Actually, it isn't a good morning.
My whole body is sore.
(Going to work with her eyes half-closed)
One, two, three.
(First up in the morning)
Be careful.
(Putting out the sign)
Good.
Gosh. My lower back.
- Goodness. I like these.
- Gosh. What are these?
- It only has egg whites.
- I love egg whites.
I love egg whites too.
Gosh. It has cheese in it.
I like egg whites because yolks are high in cholesterol.
- It's good to work at a restaurant.
- We have everything.
Do you want some super spicy sauce?
Hey, since it's easy to eat, we can take some on our way to work.
- Yes.
- I think I can eat 80 of these.
(Satisfied)
It's a good way to meet your daily protein needs.
It's hot.
- I washed my hands in hot water.
- Why do you like it hot?
- One carrot.
- I'll follow Chef Mi Hyun's order.
Let's add the onions first.
We'll add the carrots too.
Don't forget to add the onions, Head Chef.
(For some reason, Mimi is leading the prepping.)
(Here's the reason.)
(Potato cream tteoksagna)
(During the competition, )
(though it was pronounced strangely, )
(the dish got good reviews, so they upgraded it.)
(The potato cream sauce, )
(the lagu sauce, )
(and the chewy rice cake sheet are the kick to the recipe.)
(That's why yesterday, )
(they worked until late to make...)
(sticky rice cake.)
(But the problem is...)
(Prepping: Mince onions, carrots, celery, garlic, and parsley.)
(Stir-fry beef and pork. Grind cheese and pepper.)
(They have so much work to do.)
Four onions.
It works well as expected.
(Started chopping the vegetables)
Good. It'll be tasty with the celery in it.
Is it supposed to be shaky like this?
(The head chef couldn't even assemble it yet.)
(Dropping)
(Struggling as it's her first time chopping the ingredients)
Let's try it again calmly.
(Finally, she starts chopping the onion.)
(A 175cm-tall chef is all hunched over.)
(As the repetitive task continues, )
(their eyes grow vacant, )
(and their gestures grow tough.)
I want to do what I'm familiar with for the rest of my life.
I don't want to learn, open up,
and get to know a new field.
(Eun Ji starts stir-frying the beef.)
(Staring)
I like this stove.
I love how strong the heat is.
(When Eun Ji stir-fries the vegetables...)
(Peeking)
Try it, Young Ji.
(Switching places at once)
(Laughing)
- I'm the king of the kitchen.
- You're the king.
A head chef ought to stand before the heat.
(She finally found her place back.)
I can totally...
- How did you do it?
- Work the pan.
(She wants to try everything that looks cool.)
(It strangely stays the same.)
Gosh. Nice. Good.
(The vegetables, stir-fried until the moisture is cooked out, )
(and the sauteed meat are mixed together.)
Six cups of red wine.
(Red wine will add more flavors to it.)
- Add 4 cups of tomato puree.
- Add 4 cups of the puree.
Great. It already smells good.
(The ragu sauce is ready after simmering it.)
(They start making the potato cream sauce.)
We have to add the dried pumpkin now.
(The dried pumpkin will add sweetness.)
(Crunchy bacon)
We just need to simmer it down.
It's like tomato soup.
Mimi fits perfectly in the kitchen.
(Tasting the potato cream sauce)
- Hey. It's crazy.
- It's good, right?
- It's different.
- I knew it.
It's so tasty.
Let's cut the portion in half since we have too much.
(In the meantime, Yu Jin...)
(is preparing the cream butter tteok.)
It's nice and thick, Eun Ji.
Could you taste it?
(She's the tastebud of the day.)
Mimi, this ragu looks great.
- This is it.
- Hey, good job.
You'll become the queen of cream since the chestnut cream.
That's true.
(She's overwhelmed by the praise.)
(Doing a great job executing what she learned yesterday)
The smell of the bread makes me happy.
Yes.
(Next, she cuts open the gijeongtteok.)
(Since it has become an official dish on the menu, )
(she has a lonely fight against 72 pieces of gijeongtteok.)
It's perfect.
(The cream butter tteok for the morning is ready.)
(Current Time: 11:20am)
It's 11:20am. We have 1 hour until we open.
Should I try rolling the sticky rice cake?
(Yesterday...)
- Can I have it now?
- Thank you.
(While enjoying the ice cream...)
This ice cream is giving me an idea.
Do we have a machine to make sticky rice cake?
(It gave birth to...)
(Sleeping Black Sesame Torong Ice Cream.)
(Soybean powder)
(Injeolmi syrup)
(Black sesame ice cream)
(That used to be everything.)
(But a sticky rice cake blanket is added thanks to Eun Ji.)
(A new dish with added chewiness has been born.)
(Prepping at night while she had the idea)
(Mixing black sesame powder into milk)
(Filling up the Torong molds with the mixture)
(Freezing them in the freezer)
(Prepping for the Torong ice cream is done!)
- Eun Ji.
- Yes?
Will you be able to sell the ice cream for lunch?
Yes. It's simple, so I can handle it.
- Yes.
- She's a master.
Let's go.
Gosh. Hey, sticky rice cake.
(Rolling it with a pin)
(Stretching it again with her hands)
That's awesome, Eun Ji.
(Sprinkling some sugar powder)
It's so pretty, Eun Ji.
(Adding the sticky rice cake blanket she rolled so hard)
Take a photo of it, Eun Ji.
- It's so cute.
- Let me see.
It's so cute.
- It's so pretty.
- It's adorable.
- Let's put it to sleep.
(The looks passed. Now, it's time for a taste.)
How is it? Is this the one?
Is this it?
(They successfully created a new menu.)
Okay. Let's make it.
(Continuing the momentum, they put together the tteoksagna.)
Add the potato cream sauce first.
It'll be so tasty.
(Placing the sticky rice cake sheet they rolled with much effort)
(The ragu sauce is added on top of the sticky rice cake.)
It'll taste so good. It has cheese in it.
- Will you put it in the oven, Mimi?
- Yes.
(Baking it at 220°C)
It looks so tasty, Mimi.
- Does it? I'm glad to hear that.
- It does.
- Let's go.
- Thanks for the food.
Thank you.
It has to taste good.
(The cheese keeps on stretching.)
- Hey, Mimi.
- Awesome.
- It's so...
- Hey.
Is it good?
(Satisfied)
Head Chef.
- Mimi.
- It's good.
You're my type.
- Your type?
- A woman who makes...
great potato cream tteoksagna.
(Laughing)
(She got nothing but rave reviews by the employees.)
- It was so tasty.
- That was delicious.
My goodness. Seriously, Mimi.
(Epilogue)
Could you get a part-timer from Seoul?
- A part-timer?
- I want that thing that calculates.
That calculator.
- I really want the POS system.
- Can you provide us with it?
The POS system?
- Please.
- Let's use the POS system.
I was embarrassed in front of the customers.
Are there any standing tables?
- Standing tables?
- You want the POS system.
- Standing ones.
- You want part-timers.
- Standing tables.
- Standing ones, please.
- Standing?
- Regular tables with chairs.
And a waiting area.
Let's talk about this later.
(Their wishes are coming true soon!)
(Coming up next)
(The 3rd business day starts with an amazing weather.)
(They start serving the 3 new dishes!)
(Thanks to its chewy charm, )
(the new dishes are flooded with orders.)
(This is the potato cream tteoksagna.)
(You ordered the potato cream tteoksagna, right?)
(The nonstop orders...)
(lead to an early sellout.)
(The ingredients run out early too.)
(Thanks to the new menu items, their sales soar.)
(Riding the momentum, the head chef takes on a challenge.)
(Space Rice Cake Phase 2: Tteok-makase)
(Fine-dining experience at Space Rice Cake)
(Welcome to tteok-makase.)
(The chef from "Culinary Rice Cake Class Wars...")
(and the rice cake sommeliers, the servers with smiles and grace)
(A dazzling culinary feast)
(I can't believe...)
(that we're making such good-quality dishes.)
(Thanks to the full course, )
(the customer satisfaction is at an all-time high.)
(The empty dishes start to pile up.)
(However...)
(They're done with their dish and waiting for the next.)
(I'm just telling you.)
(The kitchen is backed up before they know it.)
(We're missing two, Eun Ji.)
(Are they even missing orders?)
(The wait time only gets longer and longer.)
(We're out of shrimp.)
(The kitchen becomes more chaotic.)
(It's so exhausting.)
(Their challenge to serve tteok-makase)
(How will it end?)
(Space Rice Cake)